

CONTACT

- +855882090114
- ✓ luckychappie000111@gmail.com
- Native Myanmar
- Phnom Penh City, Cambodia
- https://github.com/luckychappie
- in linkedin.com/in/ei-thandar-khaing-9401282a8

EDUCATION

COMPUTER UNIVERSITY
Jun 2012 ~ Sep 2017

• B.C.Sc (Computer Science)

SKILLS

- Laravel
- Codeigniter
- CakePHP
- Golang
- Vue JS (Nuxt framework)
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- JQuery
- Flutter (Basic)
- Javascript
- Mysql
- Cpanel Server
- Digital Oceal Server

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Japanese (N4 have no JLPT Certificate)

EI THANDAR KHAING

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I have around 6 years of experience in the web development, web design, collecting user requirements, structuring project flow and communication with customers. I have been working in both front end and backend including database structures. Mostly work as full-stack developers. I can learn faster for the project's requirements and needs.

While I enjoy working in a team and I can also work independently. I also prefer to learn new languages, technologies and I am flexible in communication.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apex IT Web Development Co.,Ltd

OCT 2017 ~ NOV 2018

Web Developer

- Building websites and maintainance using PHP, Laravel & Bootstrap.
- Designing database structures for web application
- Requirement collection and analysis, design & timeline for projects

CYA Co.,Ltd

Dec 2018 ~ May 2019

Web Application Developer

- Develop and maintain Government Assets Management Project using Codeigniter and Bootstrap
- Create web application for Gym Management Software with Codeigniter & Angular

Career-Tech Japan Co., Ltd

Jul 2019 ~ Jun 2022

Full Stack Developer

 Build company in-house E-learning and job agency projects using Laravel, CakePHP, Bootstrap, Vue (Framework - Nuxt js)

Current working projects:

- www.career-techjapan.com [Trainee appointment and recruiting]
- www.japanreadyschool.com [online course / examination / jobs]
- https://jpromyanmar.com [Job agency]

MYSOL Co..ltd

Jul 2022 ~ Feb 2023

Senior Web Developer

- Build web application from Japan using PHP (Zend Framework/ Laravel)
- · Testing and make documentation for project

Quantech Co., ltd

Mar 2023 ~ Feb 2024

Full Stack Developer

- · Customize POS project using Codeigniter
- Create E-Learning / document management/ company profile / blogs news, etc., using Laravel, Vue JS and Flutter

Flct company

Mar 2024 ~ Present

Web Developer

- Build appication web view for social media app
- · Use Vue JS and Golang